(Sheldon:)or downloadable
from my FTP server.
(Sheldon:)If you have
any questions,
(Sheldon:)here's the FAQ sheet,
(Sheldon:)or if you prefer
the human touch,
(Sheldon:)I do a live web chat called
"Apartment Talk"
(Sheldon:)on Tuesday nights.
(Leonard:)No backsies.
(Raj:)Sheldon, dinner!
(Sheldon:)What is this?
(Raj:)This is the difference
between
(Raj:)eating and dining.
(Sheldon:)Remarkable.
I'm just realizing how much
(Sheldon:)Leonard's been skating by
all these years.
(Raj:)It's not a big thing.
(Raj:)Just think of me as
a brown Martha Stewart.
(Penny(at door):)Hey, Sheldon,
(Penny(at door):)did you change
your Wi-Fi password again?
Yes, it's "Penny, get your
own Wi-Fi." No spaces.